i think we're the best storytellers i
was fired
from being in a gang black comedy is
always gonna be
based on the truth truth to powell this
morning and every single morning i've
woken up just what black again hope i
make it
oh you only voted for obama because he's
black yeah
but if we get rid of the confederate
flag
[Applause]
how am i gonna know who the dangerous
white people are
to me being a black comedian in america
means you got to stand up for something
you got to say something if i was a
white woman i would rob black dudes
black guys get arrested just for not
buying coffee
i like watching trump rallies because
for the first time in my black life i
get to see white people be embarrassed
by other white people
i was stopped by a by the cops in a cab
like oh really you're a comedian tell me
a joke i was like you just pulled over
my cap
that's the joke it's not just a
joke
to them it's real how do you celebrate
black history month sir
they need to laugh think about why the
comedy club is important
we found a place where we can just laugh
away to paint my mother was a social
worker my father was a drug dealer
they had the same clients i have to talk
to my people
and say yeah this happened to me too
white people don't let this white girl
get you okay relax this is funny
what better place to be able to tell
your story
than on a stand-up stage with freedom of
speech
and letting it just go